santroxing.com 2010-12-31

# Hyundai Motor Company :: PRIVACY POLICY

| 

Hyundai Motor India Ltd (HMIL) respects the privacy and security of the visitors to its website. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we sometimes collect information during your visits to understand what differentiates you from each of our millions of other users. In order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have prepared this Privacy Policy. This policy explains what personally identifiable information of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, how we protect your information, who has access to your information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in this information. In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this privacy policy. HMIL reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such change on our site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting. Continued usage of this website following changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes. 

This site contains links to other sites; HMIL is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.   
  
---  
|   |    
---|---  
| 

What personally identifiable information does HMIL gather/track about you through its website? HMIL may collect or require you to supply contact information (like your name, e-mail, address, city, & zip code), personal information (like profession, qualification, marital status etc.) and unique identifiers (like your password). During normal website usage we may also collect certain information about yourself, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time of your visit, pages you request, name of the internet service provider, the website or media that referred you to us etc.  
  
  |    
| 

What does HMIL do with the information? We use the data gathered to send you information. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. HMIL records this basic information about visits to its site, for systems administration, statistical and troubleshooting purposes. We use your IP address to help diagnose problem with our server and to administer our website. We use your contact information to tailor your experience at our site showing you content that we think you might be interested in and displaying the content according to your preferences.  
  
  |    
| 

How HMIL protects your information? The privacy and protection of your personal information is vitally important to us. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding your HMIL website usage are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. Despite our efforts to protect your personal information through security procedures commensurate with industry standards, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You transmit all such information at your own risk.  
  
  |    
| 

With whom does HMIL share the information? HMIL does not sell or rent personally identifiable information to any third parties. Personal information about you supplied electronically may be shared with third parties viz., affiliates, auditors, authorized dealers, legal advisers and marketing partners contracted to provide services on our behalf. HMIL as it deems appropriate may use your contact information for the use of any affiliate, dealer or third party to provide these services. HMIL may disclose information if required to do so by any law enforcing agency.  
  
  |    
| Corrections Upon request, HMIL will correct personal information that you might have disclosed and state that it is erroneous.  
  
To request a correction send an e-mail to cr@hmil.net   
© 2005 Hyundai Motor India Ltd. All rights reserved.
